<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vision</string>
    <string name="content">If you want the change, be the change!\n\n
 <p>For past so many years we have witnessed ample amount of elections in our college but no representative has ever heard the plight of this institution which was indeed once prestigious.  You might think that this might be another electoral speech but trust us this is not one of those speeches which you hear on a daily basis. </p>\n\n
We do not promise you to change the state of our college overnight but what we promise is to take small initiatives that can turn out to be a founding stone in an effort to bring back the prestige of this college which was once rated above I.I.Ts. We often complain that regular classes aren’t taking place in our respective branches. In that case, rest assured because for all such problems, your F.R along with his apt team will be going alongside you to the H.O.D of your respective branch and will surely come with the most suitable solution of your problem.  We are certainly not making any fake promises that are beyond our powers like others but what we promise is to make the most of our powers in best possible way such as minimizing number of unwanted strikes regarding delaying of exams.
\n\n\n Strike is never a prompt solution but a team of students under a qualified leader can set up a system which can address important matters related to day to day problems of hostlers regarding hygiene of mess food, clean and pure water, conditions of rooms, washrooms  etc to the concerned authorities. A highly organized team with appropriate power can start multiple clubs related to subjects such as Programming Club,  Automobiles club, Auto CAD club, Painting club, Sketching club, Web Development club, App Development club, etc in order to enhance your productivity as well as organize regular programs for the betterment of our college. \n\n
\nChoose wisely! Our future is in our hands.

    </string>
    <string name="content1">Harshit Agrawal\n
    Branch: Mining\n
        Hostel Room Number: 4/27
    </string>
    <string name="scroll">We all have something in ourselves. \n\n All it takes, is a leader to inspire us to bring it in existence. \n\n We have a dream.. a dream in which there will be no more deformities in the system.. \n\n a dream.. in which all the results will come on time \n\n a dream.. in which every student will attend his regular classes..being taught  by the finest faculties \n\n a dream.. in which we see a smile on every first year student who visits the college for the first time and sees the infrastructure. \n\n a dream.. in which every experiment being conducted under expert faculties in  sophisticated labs so to gain proper practical knowledge..not just  to fill observation tables \n\n a dream.. in which M.B.M will regain its lost prestige \n\n\n but in order to convert that dream into reality it takes a VISION to combine all the  splitted Efforts into a huge revolution. We don\'t guarantee overnight success but what we promise is gradual progress. \n\n Our ambition is to connect smart intellectuals who want appropriate change in our system. A network irrespective of caste and region, a network which consists of only and only MBMITES \t    \n\n\n          let\'s come together and unite for a better cause !!</string>
    <string name="about">We are team vision who are from different places, different societies, different religions, different castes and from different backgrounds but we are the one who want changes in the pathetic and futile system. \n\n This change is not possible without unity awareness and stand.</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">576698659202064</string>
</resources>
